[Music]
English listening test part four
designed for A2
Learners this test consists of 20
questions which are divided into four
parts I will give you a short
instruction at the beginning of each
part before we get started take a pen
and paper so you can take notes while
listening are you ready
let's get
started part one listen to two
conversations and answer the true or
false
questions hello I'm Mr Phillips hi I'm
Vanessa uh where's miss
Karen she's sick today oh no so is the
reading test today yes it is okay so
this is the Teacher book but where are
the students test papers uh they're in
Miss Karen's desk oh it's locked Now
where's the key I don't know sorry oh
well no test today then oh wait it's
right here in my coat
pocket hello John do who's that it's
Leonardo DiCaprio he's my favorite
actor so good his new movie is great
very little downside else is
on there's a concert oh it's Rihanna I
love her new album her voice is amazing
Rihanna yeah she's a famous singer oh um
how about some
sports are
you look they're my favorite tennis
players their matches are always
exciting you're a tennis fan right not
really where's the remote here you
go great a football game and it's our
favorite team you mean your favorite
team you know I'm not a football
fan true or
false
[Music]
part two listen to two people talking
about the people in their office and be
ready to answer true or false
questions welcome to the department
Robert let me show you around and tell
you about your new colleagues I'll
introduce you to them all later great
thanks so who are those people over
there that's the order management team
Helen deals with the new orders she's
the one with short dark hair in the blue
dress yeah that's right you'll probably
work closely with her while you're
learning about our ordering process got
it thanks and who's that over there the
guy who's on the phone oh you mean the
one by the window in the yellow shirt Ah
that's George he's the marketing
director and that's Selena beside him
she's responsible for the internal it
systems okay I'll try to remember all of
this I should probably be taking notes
don't worry about it for now it's just
good to put some faces to
names okay great and who do I talk to
about setting up my mobile phone with
email access is that all so Selena no
you need to talk to Sebastian who works
in Communications
he can help you that's him over there
next to the printer thanks I'll
introduce myself to him
later true or
[Music]
false
part three listen to John talking about
strange Sports and complete the
sentences Sports hold great importance
to people all around the world billions
of people across the globe are Avid fans
of soccer the world's most popular
sport however American football remains
one of the most beloved Sports in the
United States despite its relatively low
viewership in other parts of the
world some sports are so obscure that
only a few people know about them these
sports are usually popular only among
those who play or watch them here are
some of the world's most unusual
Sports One
octopush octopush also known as
underwater hockey is a challenging and
exciting sport played in swimming
pools the objective of the game is for
one team to push sh Puck across the
bottom of the pool into the goal of the
other team the sport is popular in the
UK Canada New Zealand and
Australia two
fistball fistball is a sport that has
been around for a long time but not many
people know about it it is played by two
teams each consisting of five players
both indoors and
Outdoors the game is similar to tennis
as players hit the ball with their fists
or arms over the neck net to the
opponent's side in the past fistball was
a major event at the world
games three kickball once just a
children's game kickball is now popular
among adults the rules of the game are
easy to understand similar to baseball
it is now played by many people
worldwide with approximately 20,000
Spectators following the world adult
kickball
Association four man versus Horse
Marathon the man versus Horse Marathon
started in 1980 as a race between two
men and has since become an annual event
in lorti Wells UK humans participate in
a race against horses with
riders choose the correct
option
[Music]
what
part four listen to Mary talking about
her love for cooking and complete the
sentences I love to cook you might say I
have a passion for cooking I am not a
professional chef or even a serious cook
but I love to cook I enjoy trying new
flavor combinations and Tes ing new
recipes I am excited to see a look of
satisfaction on someone's face when they
eat my food and cooking gives me time to
myself when I am cooking I can forget
about everything else and really
relax I started cooking when I was still
a young child since both of my parents
worked I often made my own dinner I
didn't mind while other kids wasted time
watching TV or playing video games I
pretended to be a
scientist the kitchen was my laboratory
and I tried making new foods with all
kinds of different
ingredients sometimes the food I made
was great sometimes it was terrible but
over the years I learned a lot about
what works and what
doesn't after some time I became a
pretty good cook and started to make
dinner for the rest of my
family sometimes they liked what I made
and sometimes they didn't but it didn't
matter to
me I was always happy to see my family
eat what I prepared and I learned a
lot I don't get to cook for my family
very often now I live far away from my
family and my friends are like my family
now but my feelings about making great
food are no different than they were all
those years
ago I love to cook a big dinner have my
friends come over to my house and see
their happy faces when they eat the food
I
prepared I think good food really brings
people together maybe that's the most
important reason I love to
cook choose the correct
option
[Music]
don't forget to share your score in the
comments
section if you haven't taken our
previous listening tests yet the
playlist link is in the description
below see you in our upcoming
videos m